

MY CONTACT

Phone

0402612672

Email

noraluk.kn@gmail.com

Address

89 LANE COVE ROAD RYDE NSW 2112

SKILLS

- Golang
- Python
- NodeJS
- Flutter
- NextJS React
- PostgreSQL
- MySQL
- Oracle
- MongoDB
- Redis

NORALUK CHOTIBUTH

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



https://github.com/Noraluk

https://fe-project-gamma.vercel.app/my portforlio

ABOUT MYSELF

I am internaltional student of macquarie university with student visa. I can work as a part time 48 hours. I have worked as a software developer for 4 years in technological companies. I can implement effective frontend and backend features which are requirements of customer and project owner. My greatest strengths are learning and responsibility for my job because I often face difficult ways to clear issues, but I can handle most problems and finish the project

EXPERIENCE

Lightnet (Thailand) Co.,Ltd | 2018-2020

Backend Developer

- Implemented users logic in marketplace and connect bank API to control money between customers and merchants
- Coded blockchain in ethereum network to swap one currency and another currency

Siam Cement Group | 2020-2022

Software Developer

- Developed by python with academicians to create reports about cement transportation
- Built and implemented mobile application for employees who took care of creating roof from zero to phase 1

KASIKORN Business-Technology Group | 2022 - 2024

Golang Developer

- Developed microservices that control point between bank and customers
- Coded unit test with coverage more than 80 percent
- Maintained and built features in back office for internal employees

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering Technology: 2015 - 2018

Thai-Nichi Institute of Technology

Master of Data science: 2024 - Present

Macquarie University